<u>abozanona@gmail.com</u> Portfolio: <u>abozanona.me</u>

# **Abdulhamid Abuzanunah**

<u>GitHub</u> <u>LinkedIn</u>

### **Professional Summary**

I'm a full stack engineer with 7+ years of experience building scalable web applications for startups and scaleups. I specialize in **Node.js**, **TypeScript**, **Go**, and **Vue 3**, with a strong track record of developing high-load, resilient systems. I also have experience in **Java** & **Angular**.

I'll work closely on your system to ensure it's scalable, secure, and built with a beautiful UI and exceptional user experience.

## **Professional Experience**

Software Engineer
Nov 2022 - Present
Freiheit.com
Hamburg

 Designed, developed, and maintained scalable enterprise microservices applications for Lidl, emphasizing performance, reliability, and clean architecture using Go and Vue 3.

- Deployed services and monitored production environments using **Kubernetes**; participated in on-call rotations via **Opsgenie** to ensure system reliability and rapid incident response.
- Contributed to system design decisions for a data transmission system between services, leveraging **Go** channels for efficient inter-service communication.

#### **Technical Lead/Team Lead**

Mar 2020 - Oct 2022

CoTeDe (outsourcing company)

Hebron

- Lead team of three developers in designing and maintaining the custom, internal systems for Stellantis (a leading global automaker and provider of innovative mobility solutions) built with Struts2 and Spring Boot.
- Led team of three developers in <u>ArabCard</u> project to develop an e-commerce site to sell/trade digital cards in the MENA region using **Angular**, **Laravel** & **MySQL**.

#### Software Developer

Nov 2018 - Mar 2020

Ceyac for digital content production

Hebron and Ramallah

- Developed a Project Management web application as a frontend **Angular** developer, while also contributing to backend development using **Java Spring Boot**.
- Developed Nitro, a custom Android launcher application designed to display targeted video ads on tablets installed in taxis, using **Java** and the **Android SDK**.

#### **Software Developer**

Sep 2023 - Nov 2024

Hob-Learning (US-based EdTech Startup)

Remote

[React]

- HobLearning is an online video platform for learning Languages. Developed the full-stack website including course management, video streaming, and subscription plans & payment.
- Migrated legacy codebase to a modern tech stack, using Go (Golang) and Vue 3.
- Containerized services using **Docker**, maintained **CI/CD pipeline** for a seamless deployment to **AWS**.
- Migrated over 10,000 users data and payments details to the new platform with zero downtime. Migrated users subscription and payment details from **Stripe** to **Paddle**.

#### **Technical Skills**

**Programming languages:** Proficient in TypeScript, Node.js, and Go. Experienced with Java, C++ and PHP. **Frameworks:** Hands-on experience with Vue3, Nuxt, Go, Angular, Laravel, Android SDK, Flutter, NodeJS, Struts2, ExpressJS, AngularJS, Wordpress, Unity3d, REST API, GraphQL, Oracle, Postgres, MongoDB, and Elasticsearch.

### **Freelancing Projects**

- Luca: <u>Browser extension</u> for synchronized users movie viewing with friends online.
- Darcom: Mobile application for users to view local stores, get points and rewards. Developed three mobile applications for stores, customers and salesmen.
   [Flutter, Nodejs]
- Tmasraf: Cashback mobile app where customers get points from shopping. I was responsible for the whole
  mobile apps development of the customers and merchants applications. [Nativescript, Nodejs]
- **HuraApp**: Ticket management Mobile app between Hura town's municipality & citizens. Developed the mobile app and connected it with the server endpoints. [Xamarin.forms]

### **Education, Honors, Awards and Competitions**

Palestine Polytechnic University B.A. in Computer Engineering

- Oct 2014 Jun 2018
- ACM PCPC (2014/15/16/17): 1st place and coach of the 3rd place team in 2017.
- ACM ACPC Competition (2017): Qualified to ACM ACPC contest in the MENA region.
- Google HashCode (2018/20): 3rd place on the Palestinian teams in 2020 (1180 place overall).
- **Hebron code jam** (2017/18): **1st and 3rd place** respectively out of ~30 Palestinian teams.
- Google Code Jam (2017/18)
- Game development: Global Game Jam (2016/17/18), Arab Game Jam (2014/16/17/19/20)